scout.me 2017-04-18

# Telenav Policies

Telenav Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs your use of certain services, product or websites offered by Telenav, Inc. ("Telenav"), including the Scout GPS application, Thinknear by Telenav, and the telenav.com and thinknear.com websites. By using our services, products, websites, or otherwise by interacting with us, you consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, please do not engage in any of these activities.

Telenav understands and respects your concerns about the use of your personally identifiable information, collected from you as a customer or visitor to our websites that identifies you as a specific person or entity ("Personal Information"). Personal Information may include name, telephone numbers including mobile telephone numbers, billing account number, Mobile Subscriber Identifier, Mobile Equipment Identifier, Network Address Identifier, IP address, and email addresses. Personal Information does not include anonymous or aggregate information, which after processing may not be associated with a specific person or entity. We believe that you should know what information about you we collect, as well as how that information is used, maintained, and, in some cases, shared. The following sets forth our privacy practices and policies, applicable to Telenav customers and visitors to the Telenav websites.

You acknowledge and understand that this Privacy Policy does not apply to our business partners or other companies that Telenav does not own or operate. For information on how other providers of products or services handle Personal Information you provide through other web sites or through the use of our services in conjunction with a third party, please consult their privacy policies.

INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AND OUR USE OF SUCH INFORMATION

The types of Personal Information and other information we may collect about you are primarily from three sources: (1) information you provide; (2) information automatically collected; and (3) information from other sources. How we use and maintain that information is described below.

1\. Information You Provide

(a) Register/Information Related to Your Account

We may collect and store Personal Information about you when you register to become a customer of our services, and when you otherwise transmit such information to us via our applications, the internet (including partner websites) or by email. For instance, to maintain and/or verify your account we may collect and store in a database your name, nickname(s), mobile phone number, mobile phone model, wireless carrier, and in certain circumstances your email address, device ID/number, the last four digits of your credit card number, credit card holder's name, billing address, and credit card expiration date.

Where you have consented, we use your billing or PayPal account information for the purpose of billing you for certain of our services, and other services offered from within certain Telenav products, and with your permission, may store such information for future transactions. In certain versions of our applications, you may also be given the option to provide a profile photo.

When you choose to access one of our applications through a Facebook log-in, we collect your name, profile picture, email, Facebook password and your Facebook contacts list with your permission. Your name will be displayed and stored within our application and your email and Facebook password will be stored to provide future access to our application. We may use this email to contact you regarding your account and/or to respond to any inquiry or feedback you submit from within our applications as described in section (b) below. If you want to revoke authorization for the application to interact with your Facebook account, you can sign out of Facebook from within the application's settings menu, remove the application from the list of permitted Apps, or turn off the Platform for Apps, Plugin and Websites from the Settings menu for your Facebook account.

When you choose to access one of our applications through a Google Sign in, we collect your email, basic profile information and Google password with your permission, which will be stored to provide future access to our application. We may use this email to contact you regarding your account and/or to respond to any inquiry or feedback you submit from within our applications as described in section (b) below. If you want to revoke authorization for the application to interact with your Google account, you can sign out of Google from within the application's settings menu.

We may also use the information that we collect about you to manage your account and provide you with customer support, perform research and analysis about your use of our products and services, to inform you from time to time by email, Short Messaging Service (SMS) message and/or within our application about products or services that we think will interest you, unless you inform us that you opt out from receiving such communications from within the email, SMS message or the application. We may share the information we collect about you and your usage activity with our third party partners for the purpose of performing research and analysis about users of our products and services.

(b) Contact Our Customer Service Representatives/In-App Feedback

We may use your email address to contact you with regard to your account, such as to communicate that it is about to expire or to confirm any change to your phone number, and to respond to any inquiry or feedback you submit via our websites by email or from within any of our applications. You may opt-out of receiving such communications using the link provided within the email.

Additionally, if you provide feedback regarding a routing or map issue within one of our applications, we may share your comments and anonymized data about your location and route with the OpenStreetMap community for purposes of improving OpenStreetMap data.

(c) Accessing Our Services

When you use any of our services, including when you use a mobile device equipped with one of our applications, you will be asked to provide certain information. We may use your mobile phone number as your account number and if you consent may provide you with a verification code via SMS message. We may also assign you a separate and unique ID number as your account number. Your account number may be stored and used to manage your account and provide you with customer support, perform research and analysis about your use of our products and services, to inform you from time to time by email, SMS message and/or within our application about products or services that we think will interest you, unless you inform us that you opt out from receiving such communications from within the email, SMS message or the application.

Some of our applications also allow you to create a personal identification number (PIN), which we store in our database, for the purpose of you logging into your account. In some cases, this PIN is generated for you automatically on your wireless device, and cannot be altered.

Some of our applications also give you the option of providing us with your home and work addresses, which we store in our database, to enable you to access readily other features of our services.

On some versions of our applications you can also create a list of "favorite" addresses that can include your home and work addresses. We store these addresses in our database so that you can access them from your mobile device, and so that should you change devices, this collection of addresses will still be available to you.

(d) Third Party Applications

Some of Telenav's services provide you with access to third party applications. When you enable a third party application, information collected by Telenav is processed under our Privacy Policy while information collected by the third party application provider is governed by its own privacy policy.

(e) Promotions

When you participate in a Telenav promotion, such as a sweepstakes or contest, you may be asked to provide your name and email address, and possibly other information such as your mailing address and telephone number.

We store this information in our database and will use it to communicate with you about the promotion. We also may use your email address from time to time to inform you about our products and services that we think will interest you, unless you inform us that you opt out from receiving such communications using the link provided within the email.

(f) Request for Information

When you request additional information about one of our services either via one of our websites or via one of our partners through which our services are offered, such as a mobile telecommunications provider, information we collect through these requests include your name, nickname(s), phone number, and email address, and if you are seeking information on behalf of your company, the name of that company. We will use this information to provide you with details about our services, and we may use this information to promote our services to you in the future, unless you inform us that you opt out from receiving such communications using the link provided within the email you may receive or by contacting support@telenav.com. To understand what a partner of ours may do with information about you in the partner's custody, you should check the privacy policy of that partner.

(g) Public Forums

If you use or link to public forums such as social networking services, blogs on Telenav or non-Telenav websites, internet bulletin boards, or chat rooms, be aware that any Personal Information you submit can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, including to send you unsolicited messages. Telenav cannot prevent the distribution and use of such information by other parties.

(h) Other Submissions

We collect Personal Information about you when you submit survey responses, a job application or resume. Such information will be used only for the stated purposes.

2\. Information Automatically Collected

We automatically receive certain types of information, some of which may be associated with Personal Information, when you visit our websites or use our products and services.

(a) Information Related to Your Location and Route or Other User Content

Each time you access the Telenav GPS Navigatorâ„¢ or ScoutÂ® service or our partnered branded versions of our Navigator services, we record your location and route information, including your point of origin (which may be your then-current location), the address of your destination, the starting time of your trip, and the route you are instructed to follow. We record your current location when your wireless device requests a rerouting (which occurs, for example, when you deviate from the specified instructions). We maintain a database with these locations and route information, and may keep such information indefinitely to improve our map coverage and to provide other features that may enhance your service capabilities, functions, and your user experience. We may periodically receive your current location from the GPS hardware associated with your wireless device for the purpose of providing enhanced services, including traffic flow data. When your location, GPS heading and speed are used for these purposes, we strip it of your Personal Information, such as your phone number, prior to storing. We may share such location data in anonymized form with our third party partners performing research and analysis about traffic conditions and road segment usage.

When your mobile device's Location Services are being used by Scout or other third party applications or your mobile operating systems services, the Scout application may periodically collect and store data about your current location along with a non-personally identifiable version of your device ID to create an anonymous profile for advertising purposes. This profile may be shared with third parties for advertising purposes. For additional information about this data usage and how to opt-out, please see below regarding geohistorical-based and interest-based advertising. Additionally, this location data may also be used by us for anonymous traffic flow data or floating car data.

When you choose to use your current GPS location for specifying the locale for a business finder search, or obtaining a map, we use your location information for the requested purpose, and then discard it. We anonymously record any search activities and results for comparative analysis. Further, we anonymously record transactions for the purpose of paying directory listing and mapping data providers.

Some versions of our applications include a location and information sharing feature that enables you to share your location or other information with another party. These location exchanges are transmitted within the application or via the internet or text messages using SMS. For example, when you create, join, or navigate to a Meet Up with the Scout application, your name, profile photo, current location and/or ETA at the Meet Up location will be displayed on a map visible by other Meet Up participants. The Meet Up and your location and/or ETA will be removed from the map visible to other participants when you delete the Meet Up. We record these location exchanges, and may keep such information indefinitely. Also, if you set up a Notification within the app, the phone numbers you provide will be automatically notified via SMS message each time you arrive at or depart from the location you select. You can turn off a Notification from within the application's settings menu.

Additionally, in some versions of our applications, you can allow our application to access the data stored in the address book and/or calendar on your mobile device. Our applications may use data from your address book or for your Facebook or Google+ contacts (if you signed in with a Facebook or Google+ sign-in) to allow you to search for and navigate to the addresses of your contacts, chat with your contacts within the application, or create a Meet Up within the application. Our applications may use calendar entry data to provide you with reminders about upcoming appointments and to provide navigation to the locations of your appointments. We will only access this data if you have given permissions for a particular Telenav application to do so, and you can revoke such permissions at any time by changing the settings on your mobile device.

When you access Telenav map and data services through a third party application, we receive and store your location information from your device along with any address or point of interest search requests along with associated destination location information. We maintain a database with locations and search information, and may keep such information indefinitely to improve our map coverage and to provide other features that may enhance your service capabilities, functions, and your user experience. Such data does not contain any Personal Information, such as your phone number.

(b) Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies on our Websites

When you visit one of our websites (including telenav.com or thinknear.com), register on one of our websites, and/or fill out a form on one of our websites we collect data from you in several ways. The types of personal data that our websites collect by themselves or through third parties, include: cookies, usage data, your name, your company name, your email address, your phone number, and other contact information.

The data that we collect from you may be used for the following purposes:

  * Analytics;
  * Registration for a Scout or other application account;
  * To respond to user inquires and customer support requests; and
  * To send emails or to contact you by other means regarding your account and/or to inform you about our products and services that may be of interest to you.

We may employ browser cookies or similar technologies to identify the computer, mobile device, or some of our services and record your preferences and other data. We use cookies or similar technologies to evaluate how our websites, devices or applications are used and to provide continuous improvement to our services, make recommendations, and complete transactions you request. Cookies may be stored locally on mobile devices or on computer servers operated or controlled by Telenav. We may use a tracking pixel, agent or other visitor identification technology that collects anonymous data about your use of some of our services. We may also use Web beacons, also known as Web bugs, which are mostly invisible small graphic images (1-by-1 pixel), in the same color as the background of the web page or an HTML email, to monitor interaction with our websites or emails. In addition, when you visit our website our systems automatically collect your IP address and the type of browser that you use. When you browse our websites our systems log the Telenav web pages that you visit. Server log files are records of activity automatically created by the server and stored. If we combine or link cookie or Web beacons with Personal Information, we will treat the combined or linked information as Personal Information under this policy. We may employ third-parties to place advertisements about our products and services on other web sites. The use of cookies, Web beacons or other similar technologies by such third parties is governed by their privacy policies.

You may limit the automatic collection of certain information through the use of cookies by our websites by disabling the cookies using your browser options. Please be aware that disabling cookies may prevent you from using specific features on our websites, such as ordering services, or maintaining an online account.

Our websites may collect data about your activity and some user identifying information, including Personal Information. This collected information is disclosed to and processed by Google and is used to enable features including but not limited to remarketing and display advertising. We use remarketing, display retargeting and search retargeting with Google Adwords to advertise online and third party vendors, including but not limited to Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. We also use Google Analytics to optimize our websites. Telenav and third-party vendors, including but not limited to Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads about our products and services based on your past visits to our website or your search history. These features are solely for purposes to allow us to maintain the interests of previous visitors and deliver advertisement content specifically targeting the visitors' previous interests and searches. You may opt-out of such advertising using the [Google Ads Preference Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences) or obtain additional information available about [Google's Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/143465?hl=en&rd=1) and [how Google uses data when you use their partners' sites or apps](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

Additionally, in connection with our thinknear.com website we use a marketing automation tool called HubspotÂ® to handle various marketing tasks, for example but not limited to, contacting visitors to thinknear.com who provided their contact information and requested additional information. HubSpot's software uses cookies to track thinknear.com visitors and contacts. You can read more about Hubspot's Privacy Policy and opt-out options [here](http://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy).

Also note that we do not have a system to comply with Do Not Track requests at this time, unless required by applicable laws or regulations.

(c) Information related to your personal interests for particular advertisements

When you search for a Point of Interest or address within our Scout applicatios or our partnered branded navigation applications, we may share your search and location data with our third party partners in order to provide you with more relevant advertisement results within the application. The information we share is de-identified so that it does not contain any Personal Information, such as your name, phone number or email address.

When Thinknear by Telenav has the opportunity to serve an ad to you on a third party mobile site or mobile application or within the Scout application, we may receive information about your device, including GPS location data or other precise location data from third party ad exchanges and/or mobile publishers, including the Scout application. The device and location data collected from users of the Scout application may be shared with third party ad exchanges. This information does not contain Personal Information and does enable us to personally identify you by name, phone number, email address, or other similar means, but may include your device ID, your IP address and the geo-location of your device at the time. This information is provided so that we can improve the relevance of the ads served to you. Any such information is shared in accordance with the third party's privacy policies and subject to their terms and conditions. We do not use such information for any purpose other than serving you with interest-based ads on behalf of advertising partners. If you would like to opt out of the use and/or sharing of such data for interest-based advertising, please contact us at [support@telenav.com](mailto:support@telenav.com) or click [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/ads-optout.html) and follow the instructions provided.

We may also obtain Precise Location Data from your use of Telenav applications (and certain other third party location based applications and use that location data) about your "geohistory", which is the geo-location of your mobile device over time along with a de-identified version of your device ID to create a profile. Additionally, in order to create a profile, we may use data about your location and online activity and interests, including things like real-world category types you visited (e.g. Shopping Mall), mobile apps with which you engage, information collected by our inventory partners and other third parties and shared with us. This will involve the use of your de-identified device ID and will not include any Personal Information, such as your name, phone number, or email address.

If you would like to opt out of the use of data for geohistorical-based and interest-based advertising by Thinknear by Telenav, please contact us at [support@telenav.com](mailto:support@telenav.com) or click [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/ads-optout.html) and follow the instructions provided.

Our third-party service providers may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites, mobile websites and/or mobile applications across your various devices, in order to provide content and advertisements about goods and services of interest to you across those various devices. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices with respect to it, please: (1) visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> or the [Ghostery Enterprise opt-out program](https://www.ghostery.com/support/global-opt-out/) to learn how to opt out of having your information collected in browsers for ad serving purposes; and (2) download the Ghostery Ad Control application, available for iOS and Android, to learn how to opt out of having your information collected in mobile apps.

(d) Other Information

When you use the voice command or entry features on our services, we record your audible utterance (what you said). We collect utterances from our entire subscriber population, organize them by what was said, and then use this information to adjust speech recognition performance parameters to improve accuracy.

We will also collect information relating to your use of and the performance of our applications, including the state of your device at the time of an error or issue with the application, and such information is disclosed to and processed by third party providers, including but not limited to Crashlytics, for purposes of collecting information about errors or issues within our applications so we may improve our applications.

We may retain any data you provide to us in an email inquiry, for the purpose of tracking the types of questions we receive.

3\. Information From Other Sources

We may obtain information about you from outside sources and add to it or combine it with your Personal Information. For example, we may request credit information when you initially subscribe for service, collect demographic and marketing data about you from third parties for marketing research and analysis to improve our products/services, obtain updated address information from our shippers, or collect information from other vendors that promote and distribute our products through their own brands.

WHEN YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE SHARED OR DISCLOSED

Telenav does not sell, rent, license or otherwise share information with unaffiliated parties except as explained in this Privacy Policy.

Consent Given/Transaction Processing

We may disclose Personal Information about you to third parties with your consent. Consent is sometimes implicit, as in the disclosure of Personal Information to third-parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf.

If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with these companies, you may contact us at: support@telenav.com.

To the Primary Account Holder

We may disclose Personal Information of an account user to the primary account holder (the party financially responsible for the account). If a business, governmental agency, or other individual obtains service for you, that entity or individual is our customer, and we may provide Personal Information about you, or your use of the service to them or others at their direction.

Third Party Services or Third Party Service Providers

Telenav offers access to a variety of resources, including but not limited to various communication tools, search services, forums, and links to other World Wide Web sites in providing its services, products and websites. We may make certain Personal Information non-personal and share it or aggregated data with strategic partners that work with us to analyze usage, provide and improve products or services, or that help us market to customers, or for similar purposes. Information that is not Personal Information or is aggregated is not subject to any restrictions of use or disclosure under this Privacy Policy.

If you take advantage of a third party's services or products offered through the use of our services, we may disclose your Personal Information to such unaffiliated third parties. These entities may use this information that you provide in the course of your use of Telenav's services (including your name, nicknames, telephone numbers, audio files, and email and mailing addresses) to promote their products and services to you. Any such Personal Information that a third party uses will be subject to their applicable privacy policies.

Some of our services and functionality are provided in conjunction with third party service providers. These third party service providers process Personal Information on our behalf and are obligated to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and other appropriate security and confidentiality measures. In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, Telenav is potentially liable.

Legal Processes

We will comply with any subpoenas, court orders or other legal processes for any of the information about you in our possession, and we may use such information to establish or exercise yours, ours, or others' legal rights, or to defend against legal claims. We also may be required to disclose Personal Information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Business Transfers

Information about you in our possession may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which your Personal Information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. Telenav does not guarantee that any entity receiving such information in connection with one of these transactions will comply with all terms of this policy.

European Union Users

Information that we collect about you may also be transferred among our various divisions and affiliated companies around the world, which may involve transfer from countries within the European Economic Area (EEA) and Switzerland to countries outside the EEA. By allowing Telenav to collect this information about you, you consent to these transfers, including transborder transmission of data covered by this Privacy Policy. As a result, that country's courts, governments or law enforcement agencies could obtain disclosure of such information under that country's laws.

Telenav complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Information from European Union member countries. Telenav has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

INFORMATION ON WIRELESS DEVICES

The Telenav software (and any upgrades, modifications, or additions thereto) that is factory installed or downloaded to, and resides upon your wireless device retains your manually entered account number and PIN, or reads it from the device. Having your carrier change the assigned phone number for your wireless device does not change the account number we maintain with regard to that device, which will result in your device not being able to access your Telenav account established using the previous phone number. If this happens, please contact Telenav customer care.

SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Telenav has implemented various physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information under our control. For instance, Telenav limits access to Telenav systems that store such information to authorized personnel. Telenav also employs the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your Personal Information when you bill on our website.

While Telenav maintains a multitude of security measures to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of your Personal Information, no security measures are absolute or wholly guaranteed. Telenav will make reasonable attempts to notify you if it determines there were unauthorized acts by third parties that violate the law or this policy, or other security breaches, or where otherwise required by law.

Telenav will maintain your Personal Information for as long as a business need exists, or as required by applicable laws, regulations, or government orders. When we dispose of Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable procedures to erase or render it unreadable.

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Telenav will not knowingly request or collect Personal Information from any person under 13 years of age without prior verifiable parental or legal guardian consent. If, however, you authorize a child to use our services or products by providing them a device associated with your Telenav service, any Personal Information associated with such use will be treated as your information in accordance with this policy. Telenav encourages parents to be involved in the online activities (including wireless Internet browsing) of their children to ensure that no information is collected from a child without parental or Guardian consent.

CUSTOMER REQUESTS FOR INFORMATION

Telenav acknowledges that individuals have the right to access the Personal Information/data that we maintain about them. Customers are entitled to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed Personal Information to any affiliated companies or third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Customers are further entitled to request access to their Personal Information under Telenav's control. To protect your privacy and security, Telenav will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before providing you access or making corrections. Good faith efforts to resolve requests to correct inaccuracies in or delete Personal Information will be made by Telenav, except where the request is unreasonable. As stated in this Privacy Policy, Telenav will not sell or share your Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. Customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies may contact us at support@telenav.com or write to the attention of Privacy Policy Officer, Telenav, Inc., 4655 Great America Parkway, Suite 300, Santa Clara, CA 95054, USA.

OTHER WEBSITES

For your convenience, this website contains links to other websites, including some websites administered by Telenav or administered by other companies on behalf of Telenav, as well as to websites unrelated to Telenav. This Privacy Policy does not apply to non-linked websites. Each website should be checked for its own privacy policy.

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Telenav may from time to time update this Privacy Policy, and we encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of the latest changes. In the event that Telenav merges with, or is acquired by another company, a change to this Privacy Policy may result. Whenever a change to this Privacy Policy is significant, we will place a prominent notice on this website, at least 30 days before the effective date.

OTHER AGREEMENTS

Telenav may enter into written product or service agreements with customers that contain specific provisions related to confidentiality, security or other handling of information. If this Privacy Policy conflicts with any provision of those terms and agreements (both US and international), those terms and agreements govern to the extent of the inconsistency. In all other instances, the terms of this Privacy Policy apply.

GOVERNING LAW

By choosing to visit this website or otherwise provide information to Telenav, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the State of California, United States of America. You also agree to arbitrate such disputes and to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Use, Terms and Conditions of Service, or other applicable agreement we have with you.

Telenav is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

UPDATE INFORMATION / REVOKE CHOICES / SUGGESTIONS / CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to Telenav through your use of our services or our websites, limit or opt-out of certain communications, revoke prior communication choices you have made, or if you have suggestions for improving this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to support@telenav.com. We will use reasonable commercial efforts to address any concerns that you may have.

CONTACT INFORMATION FOR EU USERS

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, Telenav commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Telenav at:

Telenav, Inc.  
ATTN: PRIVACY POLICY OFFICER  
4655 Great America Parkway  
Suite 300  
Santa Clara, CA 95054  
USA  
Email: [support@telenav.com](mailto:support@telenav.com)

Telenav has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ for more information and to file a complaint.

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.

In compliance with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Telenav commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information. Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Telenav at:

Telenav, Inc.  
ATTN: PRIVACY POLICY OFFICER  
4655 Great America Parkway  
Suite 300  
Santa Clara, CA 95054  
USA  
Email: [support@telenav.com](mailto:support@telenav.com)

Telenav has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-Swiss Safe Harbor to an independent dispute resolution mechanism operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.

If you believe that Telenav has not complied with this Privacy Policy in regards to your Personal Information, you may write to the Telenav Privacy Officer at the above address. In your letter, please describe in detail - in as much detail as possible - the ways in which you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy. We will investigate and verify your complaint in a timely manner.

Telenav Privacy Policy last updated as of March 24, 2017.

* * *

Back to top

Telenav Warranty and Refunds Policy

Telenav Hardware Warranties and Refunds

Telenav Bluetooth® GPS Receivers One-Year Limited Warranty 

Telenav, Inc. warrants this Telenav Bluetooth® GPS receiver against defects in material and workmanship under normal use and service for a period of one (1) year from the date of purchase by the original purchaser. This warranty is extended only to the original purchaser.

If a defect in a receiver arises and a valid claim is received by Telenav within the one-year warranty period, Telenav will, at its option, either (1) exchange the receiver with another receiver, or (2) refund the purchase price of the receiver. When a receiver is exchanged, any replacement item becomes your property and the replaced item becomes Telenav’s property. When a refund is given, the receiver for which the refund is provided must be returned to Telenav and becomes Telenav’s property.

Telenav is not responsible for your shipping and other costs to return the receiver to Telenav or its authorized representative.

This warranty does not apply to: 

  1. Damage or loss which occurs during shipment. 
  2. Damage caused by accident, abuse, misuse, flood, fire, earthquake or other external causes. 
  3. Damage caused by operating the product outside the permitted or intended uses described by Telenav. 
  4. Damage caused by service performed by anyone who is not a representative of Telenav. 
  5. Consumable parts, such as batteries, unless damage has occurred due to a defect in materials or workmanship. 

This warranty also does not apply to any item other than the receiver. Specifically, this warranty does not cover any of the accessories shipped with your receiver, including the plug-in wall charger, the plug-in car charger, the USB cable, and the installation CD. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THIS WARRANTY AND REMEDIES SET FORTH ABOVE ARE EXCLUSIVE AND IN LIEU OF ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, REMEDIES AND CONDITIONS, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, STATUTORY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. AS PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, TELENAV SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL STATUTORY OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IF TELENAV CANNOT LAWFULLY DISCLAIM STATUTORY OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES THEN TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ALL SUCH WARRANTIES SHALL BE LIMITED IN DURATION TO THE DURATION OF THIS EXPRESS WARRANTY AND TO REPLACEMENT SERVICE AS DETERMINED BY TELENAV IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION. 

No Telenav reseller, agent, or employee is authorized to make any modification, extension, or addition to this warranty. Some States do not allow limitations on how long an implied warranty lasts, and some States do not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental or consequential damages, so one or more of the above limitations may not apply to you. 

This warranty gives you specific legal rights. You may have other rights which vary from state to state. 

How to Obtain Warranty Service

To obtain service under this warranty, call Telenav at 1-88-Telenav-4 (1-888-353-6284). You will be asked for your email address for Telenav to send you a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) number and details for returning the receiver to Telenav. Alternatively, you may receive this information verbally over the phone. The receiver must be returned in the original packaging with (i) a copy of the email from Telenav identifying your RMA number, or some other writing specifying your RMA number, and (ii) proof of purchase in the form of a copy of your original receipt. (You may keep the receiver’s activation code and the installation CD.) 

Telenav Refund Policy

Telenav GPS Navigator™

Use of the Telenav GPS Navigator service (the “Telenav Service”) requires payment of a monthly fee, which includes downloads to your wireless device of the Telenav GPS Navigator software and any upgrades, modifications, or additions thereto, but does not include any hardware that may be required for certain wireless devices (such as a GPS receiver). 

Telenav will not refund any payments for the Telenav Service or any necessary hardware made directly to a cellular carrier (e.g., Sprint Nextel, AT&T, etc.) or otherwise not directly made to Telenav. Check with your cellular carrier for its policy on refunds of such payments.

If you pay for the Telenav Service or for any necessary hardware through a credit card at www.telenav.com or through a direct billing arrangement with Telenav, then you or Telenav may cancel your account at any time subject to the following policies: 

  1. If you or Telenav cancel your account within the first 30 days of activation, all charges for the Telenav Service (and any hardware purchased from Telenav that you return per Telenav’s hardware return policy and procedures) will be credited back to your credit card or otherwise refunded to you, unless your account is cancelled by Telenav for cause.
  2. For any payments for the “Telenav GPS Kit Promotion” (a free GPS receiver kit with a two-year service plan commitment), if you or Telenav cancel your account within the first 30 days and you return all hardware in the GPS receiver kit, all charges will be credited back to your credit card or otherwise refunded to you, unless your account is cancelled by Telenav for cause. Beyond the initial 30-day period, the GPS receiver kit is no longer returnable and any charges assessed for the Telenav Service are not refundable. 
  3. If you or Telenav cancel your account at any time after the first 30 days, Telenav will discontinue charging your credit card for your monthly service fee or otherwise cease assessing charges under your direct billing arrangement, but will not refund any amounts for the current or previous months of service and will not provide a refund for any hardware purchased from Telenav. In addition, Telenav will not refund any amount of prepaid service. For example, if you purchased twelve (12) months of prepaid service and cancel your account after three (3) months, there will be no refund of any amount to you on your account. 
  4. You will not be provided a refund for any month for which you were not charged for the Telenav Service (i.e., as a result of any free usage or other promotion). 

Telenav Shotgun™

If you pay for the Telenav Shotgun (“Shotgun”) through a credit card payment at www.telenav.com or through a direct billing arrangement with Telenav, then you may request a refund within the first 30 days after the date of purchase. Upon Telenav’s receipt of the Shotgun unit from you per the terms of this policy, the purchase price you paid for the Shotgun unit will be credited back to your credit card or otherwise refunded to you, along with any applicable sales tax. No refund will be made for any shipping or handling charges. The Shotgun unit for which the refund is provided must be returned to Telenav and becomes Telenav’s property.

Telenav is not responsible for your shipping and other costs to return the Shotgun to Telenav or its authorized representative.

To request a refund, call Telenav at 1-88-Telenav-8 (1-888-353-6288). You will be asked for your email address for Telenav to send you a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) number and details for returning the Shotgun unit to Telenav. Alternatively, you may receive this information verbally over the phone. The Shotgun unit must be returned in the original packaging including all original accessories and with (i) a copy of the email from Telenav identifying your RMA number, or some other writing specifying your RMA number, and (ii) proof of purchase in the form of a copy of your original receipt. The Shotgun unit and all original accessories must be in good physical and operational condition; damaged product will not be accepted for return. Telenav must receive your return of the Shotgun unit per the terms of this return policy within ten (10) days from the date the RMA number is provided to you. Failure to return the Shotgun unit in this timeframe, or otherwise not in compliance with the terms herein, will invalidate your RMA.

Telenav Connected Service™

Use of the Telenav Connected Service (“TCS”) which includes downloads to your wireless device of selected upgrades, modifications, or additions to TCS, requires payment of a monthly fee.

If you pay for TCS through a credit card payment at www.telenav.com or through a direct billing arrangement with Telenav, then you or Telenav may cancel your account at any time subject to the following policies:

  1. The first 3 months of TCS is free with your purchase of a Telenav Shotgun unit, and begins from the date of first TCS activation. If you or Telenav cancel TCS within the first 30 days of first TCS activation, all charges for TCS (and the Shotgun unit purchased from Telenav that you return per Telenav’s Shotgun return policy and procedures) will be credited back to your credit card or otherwise refunded to you, unless your TCS is cancelled by Telenav for cause.
  2. If you or Telenav cancel TCS at any time after the first 30 days of first TCS activation, Telenav will discontinue charging your credit card for your monthly service fee or otherwise cease assessing charges under your direct billing arrangement, but will not refund any amounts for the current or previous months of service and will not provide a refund for any hardware purchased from Telenav. In addition, Telenav will not refund any amount of prepaid service. For example, if you purchased twelve (12) months of prepaid service and cancel your account after three (3) months, there will be no refund of any amount to you on your account.
  3. You will not be provided a refund for any month for which you were not charged for TCS (i.e., as a result of any free usage period or other promotion). Should you or Telenav choose to cancel TCS for any reason, you shall not be entitled to any refund of or reduction in the price of the Shotgun unit (except as expressly provided under Telenav’s Shotgun return policy and procedures).

* * *

Back to top

Open Source Statement

Telenav appreciates the importance of the use of open source, and is dedicated to contributing back to the open source community. In the course of development for our products and in connection with such products, we utilize certain software from the open source community subject to the applicable open source licenses. We believe that the use of open source within our products allows us to create better products for our customers. As we work with open source software, we continue to contribute back to the open source community.

The chart below summarizes the open source that we may utilize within our products and information pertaining to such open source projects.

**Open Source Projects:**

**Open Source  
Product/Component** | **Product  
Version** | **License** | **Used In**  
---|---|---|---  
ADAPTIVE Communication Environment (ACE) |  | http://www.cs.wustl.edu/~schmidt/ACE-copying.html | • Automotive  
AFNetworking |  | https://github.com/AFNetworking/AFNetworking/blob/master/LICENSE | • iPhone  
• Clients  
AndroidSlidingUpPanel |  | https://github.com/umano/AndroidSlidingUpPanel/blob/master/LICENSE.txt | • Clients  
ASIHTTPRequest |  | https://github.com/pokeb/asi-http-request/blob/master/LICENSE | • iPhone  
• Clients  
ASN1C |  | https://github.com/vlm/asn1c | • iPhone  
• Clients  
Boost | 1.44.0 | http://www.boost.org/ | • Automotive  
c-generic-library |  | http://code.google.com/p/c-generic-library/ | • Automotive  
cJSON | 01-23-10 | http://sourceforge.net/projects/cjson/ | • Automotive  
commons-codec-1.7.jar | Apache Commons Codec 1.7 | http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-codec/ | • Automotive  
commons-collections4-4.0.jar | Apache Commons Collections 4.0 | https://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-collections/ | • Automotive  
commons-configuration-1.8.jar | Apache Commons Configuration 1.8 | http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-configuration/ | • Automotive  
commons-csv-1.0.jar | Apache Commons CSV 1.0 | http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-csv/ | • Automotive  
commons-dbcp-1.4.jar | Apache Commons DBCP 1.4 | http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-dbcp/ | • Automotive  
commons-io-2.4.jar | Apache Commons IO 2.4 | http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-io/ | • Automotive  
commons-lang-2.6.jar | Apache Commons Lang | http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-lang/ | • Automotive  
commons-logging-1.1.3.jar | Apache Commons Logging 1.1.3 | http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-logging/ | • Automotive  
commons-pool-1.4.jar | Apache Commons Pool 1.4 | http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-pool/ | • Automotive  
concurrentlinkedhashmap-lru-1.1.jar | concurrentlinkedhashmap 1.1 | https://github.com/ben-manes/concurrentlinkedhashmap | • Automotive  
Crashlytics |  | http://try.crashlytics.com/terms/ | • iPhone  
• Clients  
cURL |  | MIT License | • TeleNav GPS Navigator 7.x  
• Automotive  
DDPageControl |  | https://github.com/ddeville/DDPageControl/blob/master/LICENSE | • iPhone  
• Clients  
EASTL library |  | https://github.com/electronicarts/EASTL/blob/master/LICENSE | • Automotive  
• Clients  
Eigen | 3.1.2 | Telenav uses a modified form of Eigen 3.1.2. Both Eigen 3.1.2 and the Telenav modifications thereto are licensed under the MPL2 (<http://www.mozilla.org/MPL/2.0/>). Eigen 3.1.2 source code may be found at eigen.tuxfamily.org Telenav's modifications in source code form may be found [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/includes/Eigen-3.1.2-modified.7z). | • Automotive  
• Clients  
FMDB |  | https://github.com/ccgus/fmdb/commit/7ffd84d76b3b3b6858fbad063451a76b3dfc145a | • iPhone  
• Clients  
freetype | 2.4.8 | http://freetype.sourceforge.net/FTL.TXT | • Linux clients  
• Automotive  
geo-0.7.1.jar | Geo 0.7.1 | https://github.com/davidmoten/geo | • Automotive  
Geos | 2.1 | http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/lgpl-2.1.html | • Automotive  
glog |  | http://www.opensource.org/licenses/bsd-license.php | • All Clients  
grumpy-core-0.2.2.jar | Grumpy 0.2.2 | https://github.com/davidmoten/grumpy | • Automotive  
gson-2.2.4.jar | Gson 2.2.4 | https://github.com/google/gson | • Automotive  
gtest | 1.6.0 | http://www.opensource.org/licenses/bsd- license.php | • Internal testing  
httpclient-4.0.1.jar | HttpClient 4.0.1 | http://hc.apache.org/index.html | • Automotive  
httpcore-4.0.1.jar | HttpCore 4.0.1 | http://hc.apache.org/index.html | • Automotive  
icu4j-49.1.jar | ICU4J 49.1 | http://site.icu-project.org/ | • Automotive  
InAppSettingsKit |  | http://www.inappsettingskit.com/ | • iPhone  
• Clients  
iOS Facebook |  | http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 | • Clients  
Javascript library |  | http://www.mozilla.org/MPL/MPL-1.1.html | • Clients  
JPEG |  | BSD License | • TeleNav GPS Navigator 7.x  
• Automotive  
JSON |  | http://www.json.org/license.html | • TeleNav GPS Navigator 7.x  
libasound.so.2 | Neutrino Core OS | http://www.qnx.com/download/feature.html?programid=23675  
http://support7.qnx.com/download/download/23675/TPLTL.v2.14.Jun13-12.pdf | • Automotive  
libcpp.so.4 | Neutrino Core OS | http://www.qnx.com/download/feature.html?programid=23675  
http://support7.qnx.com/download/download/23675/TPLTL.v2.14.Jun13-12.pdf | • Automotive  
libEGL.so.1 | Core Graphics | http://www.qnx.com/download/feature.html?programid=23675  
http://support7.qnx.com/download/download/27445/TPLTL.v2.14a.Jan22-16.pdf | • Automotive  
libgflag.a | gflags | https://github.com/google/glog/blob/master/COPYING | • Automotive  
libGLESv2.so.1 | Core Graphics | http://www.qnx.com/download/feature.html?programid=23675  
http://support7.qnx.com/download/download/27445/TPLTL.v2.14a.Jan22-16.pdf | • Automotive  
libglog.a | glog | https://github.com/google/glog/blob/master/COPYING | • Automotive  
libm.so.2 | Neutrino Core OS | http://www.qnx.com/download/feature.html?programid=23675  
http://support7.qnx.com/download/download/23675/TPLTL.v2.14.Jun13-12.pdf | • Automotive  
libqnx.so | Qt 4.8.1 | Telenav uses a modified form of libQtGui.so.4. Both libQtGui.so.4 and the Telenav modifications thereto are licensed under the LGPL 2.1. (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/lgpl-2.1.html). libQtGui.so.4 source code may be found http://download.qt.io/archive/qt/4.8/4.8.1/. Telenav's modifications in source code form may be found [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/download/libqnx.so). | • Automotive  
libQtCore.so.4 | Qt 4.8.1 | Telenav uses a modified and unmodified form of libQtCore.so.4. Both libQtCore.so.4 and the Telenav modifications thereto are licensed under the LGPL 2.1. (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/lgpl-2.1.html). libQtCore.so.4 source code may be found http://download.qt.io/archive/qt/4.8/4.8.1/. Telenav's modifications in source code form may be found [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/download/libQtCore.so.4). | • Automotive  
libQtGui.so.4 | Qt 4.8.1 | Telenav uses modified forms of libQtGui.so.4. Both libQtGui.so.4 and the Telenav modifications thereto are licensed under the LGPL 2.1. (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/lgpl-2.1.html). libQtGui.so.4 source code may be found at http://download.qt.io/archive/qt/4.8/4.8.1/. Telenav's modifications in source code form may be found [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/download/old/libQtGui.so.4) and [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/download/libQtGui.so.4). | • Automotive  
libQtNetwork.so.4 | Qt 4.8.1 | Telenav uses modified forms of libQtNetwork.so.4. Both libQtNetwork.so.4 and the Telenav modifications thereto are licensed under the LGPL 2.1. (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/lgpl-2.1.html). libQtNetwork.so.4 source code may be found at http://download.qt.io/archive/qt/4.8/4.8.1/. Telenav's modifications in source code form may be found [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/download/libQtNetwork.so.4). | • Automotive  
libQtOpenGL.so.4 | Qt 4.8.1 | Telenav uses modified forms of libQtOpenGL.so.4. Both libQtOpenGL.so.4 and the Telenav modifications thereto are licensed under the LGPL 2.1. (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/lgpl-2.1.html). libQtOpenGL.so.4 source code may be found at http://download.qt.io/archive/qt/4.8/4.8.1/. Telenav's modifications in source code form may be found [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/download/libQtOpenGL.so.4). | • Automotive  
libQtXmlPatterns.so.4 | Qt 4.8.1 | Telenav uses modified forms of libQtXmlPatterns.so.4. Both libQtXmlPatterns.so.4 and the Telenav modifications thereto are licensed under the LGPL 2.1. (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/lgpl-2.1.html). libQtXmlPatterns.so.4 source code may be found at http://download.qt.io/archive/qt/4.8/4.8.1/. Telenav's modifications in source code form may be found [here](http://www.telenav.com/legal/download/libQtXmlPatterns.so.4). | • Automotive  
libsocket.so.3 | Networking Technology | http://www.qnx.com/download/feature.html?programid=23675  
http://support7.qnx.com/download/download/23675/TPLTL.v2.14.Jun13-12.pdf | • Automotive  
log4j-1.2.17.jar | Apache log4j 1.2.17 | http://logging.apache.org/log4j/1.2/ | • Automotive  
lucene-analyzers-common-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-analyzers-icu-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-analyzers-phonetic-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-analyzers-smartcn-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-analyzers-stempel-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-core-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-queries-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-queryparser-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-spatial-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
lucene-suggest-4.5.0.jar | Apache Lucene 4.5 | http://lucene.apache.org/ | • Automotive  
MarqueeLabel |  | https://github.com/cbpowell/MarqueeLabel/blob/master/LICENSE | • Clients  
MD 5 hash tool |  | https://github.com/Azure/azure-mobile-apps-net-files-client/blob/master/LICENSE.txt | • Client  
Microsoft Visual Studio 2005/8 runtime libraries |  | http://download.microsoft.com/documents/useterms/Visual%20Studio_2008$%20Professional%20Edition_English_473a7e16-65dc-4cfb-8f44-ebdd93cb1d3d.pdf | • Automotive  
mockcpp | V2.6 | http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl.html | • Internal Testing  
OHAttributed Label |  | https://github.com/AliSoftware/OHAttributedLabel/blob/master/LICENSE | • iPhone  
• Clients  
opennlp-maxent-1.5.3.jar | Apache OpenNLP 1.5.3 | http://opennlp.apache.org/index.html | • Automotive  
opennlp-tools-1.5.3.jar | Apache OpenNLP 1.5.3 | http://opennlp.apache.org/index.html | • Automotive  
OpenSSL |  | http://www.openssl.org/source/license.html | • Automotive  
• iPhone  
• Clients  
PhoneGap | 0.9.3 | http://www.phonegap.com/about/license/ | • TeleNav GPS Navigator 7.x  
PNG |  | http://www.libpng.org/pub/png/src/libpng-LICENSE.txt | • Automotive  
protobuf |  | http://www.opensource.org/licenses/bsd-license.php | • TeleNav GPS Navigator 7.x  
protobuf-net r640 |  | https://code.google.com/p/protobuf-net/downloads/detail?name=protobuf-net%20r640.zip&can=2&q= | • Clients  
protobuf-objc |  | https://github.com/alexeyxo/protobuf-objc/blob/master/src/runtime/Classes/AbstractMessage.h | • Clients  
Protocol Buffers | 2.3.0 | http://opensource.org/licenses/BSD-3-Clause | • Automotive  
QT | 1.1.4 | http://qt.nokia.com/products/licensing/ | • Test frameworks  
Quattroshapes |  | https://github.com/foursquare/quattroshapes/blob/master/LICENSE.md | • Clients  
• Website  
REFrostedViewController |  | https://github.com/romaonthego/REFrostedViewController/blob/master/LICENSE | • Clients  
SBJson |  | http://superloopy.io/json-framework/ | • iPhone  
• Clients  
SBJSON | V3.0.4 | http://www.opensource.org/licenses/bsd-license.php | • iPhone  
• Clients  
SGI SI GLU | 2.0 | http://oss.sgi.com/projects/FreeB/SGIFreeSWLicB.2.0.pdf | • Automotive  
SlidingMenu |  | https://github.com/jfeinstein10/SlidingMenu/blob/master/LICENSE.txt | • Client  
spatial4j-0.4.jar | Spatial4J 0.4 | https://github.com/locationtech/spatial4j | • Automotive  
speex |  | http://www.xiph.org/licenses/bsd/speex/ | • TeleNav Navigator  
• Hybrid clients  
sqlite | V3.7.9 | http://www.sqlite.org/copyright.html | • Clients  
• Automotive  
sqlite-jdbc-3.8.7.jar | Sqlite JDBC 3.8.7 | https://github.com/xerial/sqlite-jdbc | • Automotive  
Stemmer â€“ Snowball |  | http://opensource.org/licenses/bsd-license.html | • Automotive  
Tapjoy |  | https://www.tapjoy.com/sdk/license | • iPhone  
• Clients  
threadpool |  | http://threadpool.sourceforge.net/license.html | • Clients  
Tinyxml |  | http://www.grinninglizard.com/tinyxmldocs/index.html | • Clients  
• Automotive  
TMCache |  | https://github.com/tumblr/TMCache/blob/master/LICENSE.txt | • iPhone  
• Clients  
VerifyStoreReceiptiOS |  | https://github.com/rmaddy/VerifyStoreReceiptiOS/blob/master/LICENSE | • iOS Clients  
WriteableBitmapEx | 1.0.5 | http://writeablebitmapex.codeplex.com/license | • Clients  
zlib | 1.2.5 | http://www.gzip.org/zlib/zlib_license.html | • Clients  
• Automotive  
  
Telenav Open Source Statement last updated as of January 20, 2015.

* * *

Back to top
